liveninja.com 2015-03-22

# Privacy | LiveNinja

**LIVENINJA**

**PRIVACY POLICY**

**September 25, 2012**

We are committed to keeping your personal information private.Please review this Privacy Policy, our Terms of Service (“ToS”), and any other rules or policies posted to the Site which also govern your visit and use of the website [www.liveninja.com](http://www.liveninja.com/)(the “Site”). This Privacy Policy covers the collection, use, and disclosure of personal information that may be collected by us anytime you interact with Site, such as when you visit our Site, when you register an Account or when you contact our support services. Please take a moment to read the following to learn more about our information practices, including what type of information is gathered, how the information is used and for what purposes, to whom we disclose the information, and how we safeguard your personal information.

Please read this Privacy Policy carefully before registering an account on the Site ("Account"), submitting any information or using the various services we provide, as defined below, so that you are aware of your legal rights and obligations with respect to the Site or MEETOOU LLC and any of its affiliates, parents and subsidiaries (individually and collectively, "we," "us," “our” or "MTU").     

Access to the Site is void and unauthorized where prohibited by applicable law or regulation.

**BY USING THE SITE OR USING OUR SERVICES, YOU (I) SIGNIFY YOUR IRREVOCABLE ACCEPTANCE OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY; AND (II) REPRESENT THAT** **YOU ARE EITHER MORE THAN 18 YEARS OF AGE, AN EMANCIPATED MINOR, OR POSSESS LEGAL PARENTAL OR GUARDIAN CONSENT, AND ARE FULLY ABLE AND COMPETENT TO ENTER INTO THE TERMS, CONDITIONS, OBLIGATIONS, AFFIRMATIONS, REPRESENTATIONS, AND WARRANTIES SET FORTH IN THIS PRIVACY POLICY, AND TO ABIDE BY AND COMPLY WITH THIS PRIVACY POLICY. IN ANY CASE, YOU AFFIRM THAT YOU ARE OVER THE AGE OF 13, AS THE SITE IS NOT INTENDED FOR CHILDREN 13 YEARS OF AGE OR UNDER. IF YOU ARE 13 YEARS OF AGE OR UNDER** **, YOU ARE NOT ALLOWED TO USE OR EVEN ACCESS THE SITE AND/OR THE SERVICES OR TO CREATE AN ACCOUNT.**

Further **,** if you do not agree with this Privacy Policy, or any of its terms, please do not provide us with your personally identifiable information (“PII”) for example your full name, email address, mailing address, telephone number, or credit card number or any other personal information capable of being associated with you individually through one or more identifiers.

Our business changes constantly, and our ToS, any rules posted on the Site, as well as this Privacy Policy may change too.You should check the Site frequently to see if there are recent changes.MTU reserves the right to revise this Privacy Policy at any time. Your continued use of the Site shall be deemed an irrevocable acceptance of any such revisions.

Unless stated otherwise, our current Privacy Policy applies to all information that we have about you. ****The above sentence notwithstanding, this Privacy Policy only applies to information collected by MTU.

1. **Description of the Site.** The Site enables individual with knowledge, experience or expertise in a variety of subjects and fields(“Expert” aka Ninjas) to engage with, communicate to and teach interested individuals (“Students” aka grasshoppers) such knowledge or expertise. The Site provides Experts and Students with a variety of tools to facilitate such engagements, classes and sessions (together “Classes”) including, but are not limited to, directory listings, payment facilities, live and recorded video capabilities, advertising options, scheduling management and various other advanced communication capabilities. All activities and capabilities offered by or through the Site shall individually and collectively be referred to as “Services”. ****

“Users” shall be defined as any Student, Expert or other user or visitor of the Site or its Services

Users may, where and if available, submit any photograph(s), video(s), image(s), email, text, and/or comment(s) or other content to the Site (“Submission(s)”).

2. **What information does the Site collect?**

**Visitor Activity.** Visitors to the Site may choose to browse, search and examine any publically available information on the Site without registering with the Site or registering an Account.When you visit our Site as a non-registered visitor, we collect only information you provide or submit to the Site directly, information you send to us by email, information and messages you send or post through our accounts on third party social networks (such as Facebook, YouTube or Twitter), comments you post or messages you send through any service we may provide. The foregoing statement not withstanding, our servers may recognize and collect non-registered visitors’ domain names, IP addresses and any information on pages visited. ****

**Account Activity**. In order to have access to certain services and features available on the Site, Users, both as Experts and Students, may be required to register and setup an Account.We may ask for and collect some PII when you create an Account. When registering an Account with the Site, you agree to provide accurate, current and complete information about yourself ("Registration Data") as prompted by our registration form. Registration Data may include, but is not limited to, first and last name, phone number, address and e-mail address. After you setup an Account, we also collect a variety of information and PII depending on the services and features you use and Classes you take.

**Content Uploaded to the Site.** Any PII or Submissions that you voluntarily disclose on the Site is collected by us.This may include any information you submit as part of your Account profile as well as Submissions you make as comments on the Site. In addition, some information (for example, PII contained in your comments, messages or profile pages, if any) may become publicly available and can then be collected, viewed and used by third parties. The above not withstanding, MTU does not record information streamed live via our video conferencing services.

**Usage Information.** We may collect information about your usage of the Site, such as when you use the Site, the Submissions you make, the information you review, the frequency and size of data transfers, as well as information you display or click on in the Site.If you are logged in we may associate this information with your Account.

**Communications.** We collect information you submit to any of our public forums, such question/answer forums and blog comments. MTU does not record any real-time video conferencing and classes; however, such forms of communications do result in the collection of personally identifiable information necessary to enable these services. For example, our servers may retain copies of email or instant message communication sent Experts and Students. Also, our system may retain some logs of video and voice communications made through our Site. Please review the information provided with any particular service of feature on the Site to ascertain how communication will take place and the level of privacy inherent in the service. Never assume that any communication or interaction, whether by email, text, instant messaging, voice or video provided by or through the Site assures privileged or confidential communications. 

**Financial Information:** Some of the Site’s Services require billing through a User’s PayPal account. Financial information is not collected by the Site unless you specifically opt-in as described below. MTU offers an opt-in option that enables the Site to record a User’s PayPal login information in order to expedite future transactions. Unless you opt-in to enable the Site to record such information, MTU will not store any of the financial information you provide as part of any transaction. 

**Surveys & Newsletters.**We may now or in the future send or run surveys or provide newsletters to our Users. At such time we may request certain PII such as name, email address and demographic information (such as zip code, age, or income level). 

**Click-Through URLs.** In some of our email we may use a “click-through URL” linked to content on the Site. When Users click one of these URLs, they pass through our web server before arriving at the destination web page. We may track this click-through data to help us determine interest in particular topics and measure the effectiveness of our communications. 

3. **How do we use the information you provide us?** We use PII such as your contact information to provide you with the various services and features and to potentially serve you with advertising while on the Site. **Except as provided herein,** **MTU does not sell or rent your PII information to other marketers.** All information that you submit to us is governed by this Privacy Policy, the ToS and any other rules.

Any PII collected as a result of communications initiated through our Site, are used to enable Site services and features. For example, information collected by our servers may be used to direct communication between Experts and Students. 

We may share information collected including your PII with our agents, representatives, contractors and service providers so they can provide us with support services such as authorization of credit card, e-mail origination, support services, customer relationship management services and order fulfillment. 

We may share information collected including Student PII with Experts on the Site for the purpose of enabling services such as communications. Experts may also receive PII of all Students who comment, rate or opine on their services. 

Information provided by an Expert as part of their online Account profile and designed to promote the Expert’s business and expertise may be publicly displayed. 

The email address used or the user-name you create during registration may be displayed to other Users when you provide Submissions such as commenting and other Users can contact you through comments, blogs, chat, or forums.Such PII may also be shared when attending Classes given to more than one Student at a time. Any public Submissions that you provide through the Site, such as commenting, may be redistributed through the Internet to other website and other media channels, and may be viewed by the general public. 

Unless you opt-out, we may use your e-mail or other PII to send commercial or marketing messages without your further consent.Be advised that we use your e-mail address and other contact information provided by you to contact you regarding your Submissions.We may also use your e-mail address without further consent for non-marketing or administrative purposes (such as notifying you of major Site changes or customer service purposes). 

You may opt-out at any time by changing your preferences and editing your profile online. 

We use both your PII and certain non-PII (such as anonymous user data, cookies, IP addresses, browser type, click stream data, etc.) to improve the quality and design of the Site and to create new features, promotions, functionality and services by storing, tracking, analyzing and processing User preferences and trends, as well as User activity and communications. 

We use information collected during submission of Surveys and signups for Newsletters to send both the information as requested and additional information about our company, Site or Services. Further, the information collected, including any demographics, is used to learn more about the types of people who visit our Site and improve our services.

If any financial information is collected it will be used only to bill you for services or features offered on the Site.If you used a credit card to pay for any service, your credit card information may be subject to verification by the issuing credit card company or other third party company.Unless you give us permission at the time such information is collected, this information will not be used for any purpose except for the fulfillment and record keeping of current and future transactions.

Experts are third parties unrelated to MTU. In an attempt to provide increased value to our Users, we may choose various third party web Site, such as an Expert’s website, to link to, and/or frame within the Site. We also may participate in co-branding and other relationships to offer e-commerce and other services and features to our Users. We have no control over these linked Sites, each of which has separate privacy and data collection practices independent of us.We encourage you to read the policies of these Experts and other third party websites. By engaging, retaining or communicating with Experts through our Site, you consent to our providing your PII to those Experts or other third parties. **** Data collected by our co-brand partners or third party websites (even if offered on or through our Site) may not be received by us. As such, we have no responsibility or liability for the independent policies or actions of third parties, and are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of any such website. These linked sites are only for your convenience and you therefore access them at your own risk. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of the services and the links placed upon each of them and therefore request any feedback. 

Further, any linking with any other web site is neither an endorsement of that site nor any of the products or services that may be offered on that site. 

**Note:** Your PII or financial information may be passed on to a third party in the event of a transfer of ownership or assets of MTU or a bankruptcy. We may also disclose PII or financial information when we determine that such disclosure is necessary to comply with applicable law, to cooperate with law enforcement or to protect the interests or safety of MTU or other visitors to the Site.Whenever PII or financial information is disclosed under this paragraph, we may also disclose your demographic information on a non-anonymous basis. 

4. **How does MTU Protect Users Personal Information?** We implement a variety of security measures to ensure the security of your PII on our systems.When you enter sensitive financial information, such as credit card numbers, we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). Please be aware that emails or other messages you send to us are not necessarily secure against interception and you should not include sensitive information in those messages. We generally will not ask for your credit or debit card number, password or other sensitive information in an email and you should assume that if you get such a request, it might be fraudulent.

Except for the SSL transmissions, the Site is not encrypted. Access to your Account profile is restricted by your password.

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your PII, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

Third parties may unlawfully attempt to intercept or access transmissions or private communications and other Users may abuse or misuse your personal information that they collect from the Site.Although we work very hard to protect your privacy, we do not promise, and you should not expect, that your personal information or private communications will always remain private.

**7.Individuals under 13 years of age.**

Pursuant to the provisions of the 1998 Federal Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (“COPPA”), our policy is to refuse individuals 13 years of age or under to submit information to the Site.We therefore do not knowingly collect personal information from individuals 13 years of age or under.

8. **Does MTU Use Cookies?** We use "cookies" (small pieces of data we store for an extended period of time on your computer, mobile phone, or other device) to make the Site easier to use, to improve our advertising, and to protect both you and the Site.We also use cookies to record Users' preferences, record session information, customize website content and alert Users to new items of interest. We may store your email address or login ID to recognize you every time you return to the Site.

9. **How do you change PII provided or OPT-OUT?** MTU gives registered Users an option for modifying or removing their information from our database. To update, modify or delete the information that we have on file for you, you may edit your online Account profile.We will comply with your requests as reasonably as we can. Please note that we require some PII for billing purposes. If you wish to delete certain PII required for Account maintenance such as your name, e-mail address or billing information, you may be required to terminate your Account.However, please note, that while you may remove your PII from the Site at any time, you acknowledge that we may retain archived or cached copies of your PII. 

10. **How Long Do We Keep your Information?** Except as otherwise provided below, User’s PII is maintain only as long as he/she maintain an Account with the Site. The above not withstanding, contact information may be maintained by us after an Account has been terminated for marketing and promotional purposes.

11.By visiting and using the Site, you consent to the collection and use of information by us as set forth in this Privacy Policy.If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes within this page so Users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.

Be sure to review our Privacy Policy, ToS and any rules regularly so that you will be aware of any changes to them.Please remember that your continued use of this Site, and/or maintenance of an Account after changes or revisions have been made constitute your acceptance of such updates.

12.If you have any questions about the Privacy Policy of the Site, please contact us at:

MEETOOU LLC.

6815 Biscayne Blvd

Suite 103-172

Miami, FL 33138
